Aisha D. Coles

Federal Way, WA	Phone: 206-755-4466	Email: coles aisha@yahoo.com
-----------------	---------------------	------------------------------

Self-Taught web developer with 5+ years of Administrative Assistant experience. Background knowledge in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Version Control, and Responsive Web Design. Ready to grown and own my skills as a web developer in the working field.

Professional Experience

20	17 to present	Marketing/ Office Assistant	C&L Catering Distribution/ Enterprise Inc. SeaTac, WA
----	---------------	-----------------------------	--

- Responsible for maintaining and editing company marketing products (prints, website, emailed campaigns and catalogs)
- Handling everyday office duties (answering phones, data entry, filing, etc.) and some warehouse duties (located products, fulfilling orders and receiving products).
- Providing excellent customer service to clients and vendors.
- Cleaning and maintaining front office area.
- Implementing new procedures and policies.
- Handled Office Manager duties in their absence (receiving, invoices and purchasing).

		`
2016 to 2017	Office Coordinator	Runberg Architecture Group Seattle, WA

- Acts as the "first impression" of the firm by greeting callers and guests, and extending gracious hospitality
- Functions as an overall office juggler in support of a busy firm environment
- Takes ownership of administrative duties such as processing mail and packages, running errands, managing conference room usage, maintaining office equipment, purchasing office supplies, mailings and list work, kitchen duties, facilities, materials library and working with vendors, filing and archiving
- Accounts Payable work in QuickBooks
- Provide support in marketing activities
- Provides executive assistance to Principals, architects and Office Manager as needed

2014 to 2016	Minerilary Unerations Assistant	Bonney-Watson Washington Memorial Corp.	
		SeaTac, WA	

- Lead designer in creating and marketing memorial merchandise products.
- Personal administrative assistant to 4+ funeral directors.
- Assisting with new employee training.
- Responsible for handling confidential and time sensitive documents.
- Communicate with new clients and current clients by phone, email, and in person.
- Created, updated, and processed various tracking logs for monthly and yearly reports.
- Assist in management related projects and execution of new procedures.
- Coordinate inventory orders and distribution of supplies.
- Main point of contact for question related to multiple departments within the company.
- Backup for front desk admins at the company's several locations.

Self-Taught Coding Education

2019 to present	Codebyte	Online Challenges	JavaScript problem solving
2017 to present	CodeAcademy	Online Courses	HTML, CSS, JavaScript, PHP
2018 to 2018	Udacity	Online Course	HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Version Control, Accessibility, Git
			Control, Accessionity, Git

Aisha D. Coles

Federal Way, WA	Phone: 206-755-4466	Email: coles aisha@yahoo.com
-----------------	---------------------	------------------------------

Education

2009 to 2013	Wesleyan College	Macon, GA	Bachelor's Degree in Spanish
2008 to 2009	South Seattle CC	Seattle, WA	College and High School Credits
2005 to 2009	Foster High School	Tukwila, WA	High School Diploma

References Upon Request.